(Awkward guy:)But how did you get her
to go out with you?
(Leonard:)Well, she moved in
across the hall.
(Penny:)And he started
to slowly wear me down.
Mm-hmm.
(Leonard:)Like a river carves a canyon.
(Penny:)Yeah, except the river kept
showing me his Pokémon cards.
(Red-haired guy:)Ready to go?
(Awkward guy:)Hang on.
This guy's telling me
(Awkward guy:)how he got the Serial Ape-ist
girl to marry him.
(Red-haired guy:)This guy?
(Red-haired guy:)But he's wearing
a change maker.
(Penny:)I think it's hot.
(Leonard:)That's right.
(Leonard:)I'm her change daddy.
(Howard:)What was I thinking?
(Howard:)Wolowitzes are not
a lifting people!
We tip the lifting people!
(Bernadette:)Do we really
have to sit for hours
(Bernadette:)in the emergency room?
(Bernadette:)They're just gonna give you
ice and Advil
(Bernadette:)like last time.
(Howard:)You're gonna feel terrible
when I'm in a wheelchair.
(Howard:)Which, by the way,
would fit easily in the back